Guide to the Lynn Saville Photographs, 1972-2015 and undated RL.01142
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Lynn Saville photographs
1972-2015 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Saville, Lynn
RL.01142
21.5 Linear Feet 20 boxes 295 items
The collection dates from 1972 to 2015 and consists of over 200 large color and black-and-white photographic prints of nighttime scenes selected from the work of photographer Lynn Saville in urban centers such as Paris, Rome, Venice, New York City, Durham, North Carolina, Los Angeles, Vermont, and other locations. The collection also includes 30 portraits of artists, feminists, writers, family members, and other individuals, as well as self-portraits. Supplemental materials such as book reviews and book maquettes round out the collection. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Biographical Note
Lynn Saville is a photographer based in New York City. She was born in Durham, North Carolina in 1950 and received a B.A. from Duke University in 1971 and an M.F.A. from the Pratt Institute in 1976. Her photographs are held in the Denver Art Museum, the Brooklyn Museum of Art, Oxford University's Bodleian Library, the New York Public Library, and many other museums and libraries. In 2017 she was awarded a commission by the New York City MTA Arts to document "Grand Central Revealed," which culminated in a three-year exhbit.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Original audiovisual materials in the Supplemental Materials series are closed to use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Lynn Saville photographs were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2002 and 2005, and 2016, and as a purchase in 2015.
Collection Overview
The collection consists of selections of work from photographer Lynn Saville's portraiture and night photography from urban America, dating from 1972-2015. Formats include traditional darkroom gelatin silver prints, color prints, and a small number of digital prints. Sizes range from 11x14 to 20x24 inches.
The Portraits series includes 30 images of poets, photographers, family members, friends, and prominent women such as Barbara Jordan, Adrienne Rich and Bella Abzug. The collection's primary focus, however, is Saville's more recent work, housed in the Nocturnal Photography and Dark City series, containing 205 photographs of night scenes in the United States and Europe, particularly New York City (with a focus on Brooklyn) and Paris. Other locations include Los Angeles, North Carolina, Vermont, Paris, Rome, and Venice.
Selected images are also available online as part of a Duke University Libraries digital exhibit.
There is also a Supplemental Materials series which includes printed matter such as articles and book reviews, and a documentary film directed by Anna Borden about Saville's career and photography (2003).
Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Related Material
Night Vision: Photographs of William Gedney and Lynn Saville [Online exhibit]
Rare Book, Manuscripts and Special Collections Library, Duke University
Cities and towns -- United States; Metropolitan areas -- United States -- Pictorial works; Night photography; Photographers -- United States; Women -- Portraits; Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.) -- Pictorial works; Los Angeles (Calif.) -- Photographs; New York (State) -- Photographs; New York (N.Y.) -- Photographs; North Carolina -- Photographs; Paris (France) -- Photographs; Rome (Italy) -- Photographs; Venice (Italy) -- Photographs; Vermont -- Photographs; Mock-ups; Black-and-white photographs; Color photographs; Digital prints; Portrait photography; Saville, Lynn; Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University)
- Portraits, 1972-2005; 2 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Thirty 11x14 inch gelatin silver prints portraying poets, photographers, women in politics, family members, and friends. The series includes one platinum print portrait of Saville taken by Lois Conner. Captions are taken from the prints.
  - 11x14 gelatin silver prints (11x14), primarily portraits, 1977-1995, 11 prints
    - Bill Winfield, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Muriel Rukeyser, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Sterling Plump, poet, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Raymond Patterson, poet, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Galway Kinnell, poet, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Juanita Kreps, Secretary of Commerce, in her office, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Dr. Rosalyn Yalow, Nobel Prize winner, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Robert Bly, poet, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Gwendolyn Brooks, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Bella Abzug, New York Political, 1977 (Box 1)
    - French Ballet School, 1992 (Box 1)
  - 5x7 platinum print, ca. 1976
    - Portrait of Lynn Saville (taken by Lois Conner), ca. 1976 (Box 1)
  - 11x14 gelatin silver prints, primarily portraits, 1972-1999, 16 prints
    - Adrienne Rich, 1993 (Box 2)
    - Susan Sontag, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Thom Gunn, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Eugenia Saville, my mother, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Philip Fried, poet, my husband, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Curtis Saville, my brother, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Maria Karolyi, friend, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Lloyd Saville and Eugenia Saville, my parents in Vermont, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Self portrait in Vermont, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Girl I met along the road in Vermont, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Lawrence, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Lloyd Saville, my father in Vermont, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Vermont Neighbors, Dot and Gordon Slade, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Circus boy, Ringling Brothers, Barnum and Bailey Circus, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Beth Caspar, artist and friend, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Trapeze artist, circus, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Ed Malinowski, artist and friend in Vermont, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Gelatin silver prints, irregular sizes, 1978, 2 prints
    - Barbara Jordan, 10 1/8 x 12 5/8, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Philippe Halsman, photographer, 9 x 12 5/8, 1978 (Box 2)
- Nocturnal Photography, 1973-2005 and undated, bulk 1994-2005; 13 boxes
  The series contains 205 16x20 and 20x24 prints. There are color photographs, gelatin silver, and a few Iris prints (digital prints). Matted prints are located at the end of the series. Approximately 75 prints show scenes from New York City, especially Brooklyn. There are also numerous images shot in Paris. Other locations include Rome, Venice, North Carolina, Vermont, Los Angeles, and New York State. Captions are taken from the prints, with information added in some cases.
  - 16x20 gelatin silver prints, 1989-2003 and undated, 17 prints
    - Venice: Palazzo Rio Canonico, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Venice: Rialto Bridge with shadows, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Venice: Gondolas on the Grand Canal, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Venice: Bridge of Sighs, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Venice: Phil sleeping, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Bowing ballerina (New York City ballet), 1989 (Box 3)
    - The violinist, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Three ballerinas exiting, undated (Box 3)
    - Cirque d'Hiver, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Udaipur rooftops, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Cars near Seine, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Steps to the Tuileries, 2002 (Box 3)
    - The Villa Borghese, Rome, 2002 (Box 3)
    - Tiber River, Rome, 1998 (Box 3)
    - The Louvres and Tuileries, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Riverside Drive, 2003 (Box 3)
    - Bill's back yard, 1993 (Box 3)
  - 16x20 gelatin silver prints, 1973-2001, 25 prints
    - Sherry Netherland, 1995 (Box 4)
    - Cow and Police Vehicle, Central Park, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Violinist and Pianist, Derby Line Opera House, 1973 (Box 4)
    - West Charleston, Vermont, 1996 (Box 4)
    - West Charleston, Vermont (II), 1996 (Box 4)
    - Fearington Road, Chapel Hill, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Wolfe's Windows, West Village, NYC, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Planetarium, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Mona's rooftop, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Senhora Del Monte, Lisbon, Portugal, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Titanic at the Drive In, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Times Square, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Tribeca New York, 1995 (Box 4)
    - Rhinebeck, New York, 1995 (Box 4)
    - Apartment 45, New York (last night there), 2000 (Box 4)
    - Middleton Plantation, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Middleton Plantation (II), 1997 (Box 4)
    - Brewster, New York, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Derby, Vermont, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Tree at Echo Lake, Vermont, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Kitty Hawk beach, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Poughkeepsie, New York, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Los Angeles from Griffith Park Observatory, 1997 (Box 4)
    - Griffith Park Observatory, Los Angeles, 1997 (Box 4)
  - 16x20 gelatin silver prints, 1989-2000 and undated, 18 prints
    - La Madeleine, Paris, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Man along the Seine, Paris, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Across the tracks, Durham, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Cornwallis Road, Durham, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Paul's driveway, Pittsfield, MA, 1995 (Box 5)
    - Truck at Echo Lake, undated (Box 5)
    - Skating House, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Mom's backyard, Durham, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Beach fire, Beach Haven, NJ, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Roof Garden, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Face at Columbus Circle, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Brooklyn window, undated (Box 5)
    - Phil's shadow, New York City, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Hellgate and Triboro Bridge, 2000 (Box 5)
    - The Cooper Hewitt, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Mount Pisgah, stars, Vermont, 1994 (Box 5)
    - Siphnos Street, Greece, 1993 (Box 5)
  - 20x24 color prints, 1999-2005, 23 prints
    - Chapel Hill, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Basin Street, 2004 (Box 6)
    - The Terraced Bridge (green), 2004 (Box 6)
    - Amsterdam rain, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Cleveland overpass, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Storm, Westport, 2005 (Box 6)
    - La Samaritaine, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Tarrytown, NY, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Metropolitan roof, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Warehouse with arches, 2003 (Box 6)
    - 1160, Los Angeles, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Musée Entrée, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Bethesda fountain, 2004 (Box 6)
    - 1814, Los Angeles, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Arcade shadows, Paris, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Parachute jump, Coney Island, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Rue Jarante, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Chartres, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Crossing, Paris, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Post No Bills, Times Square, 1999 (Box 6)
    - The tobacco warehouse, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Whippoorwill Lane, Chapel Hill, 2005 (Box 6)
    - The Yellow House, Westport, 2005 (Box 6)
  - 20x24 gelatin silver prints, 1996-2002, 12 prints
    - Stop/Dead End, Red Hook, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Sheeps' Head Bay, Brooklyn, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Bicyclist on Seabring and Richards, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Garden at Pierpoint Street, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Bicycle on Front Street, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Gowanus Garden, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 7)
    - House on Sydney Place, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Building on Gowanus Canal, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Marginal Street steam pipe, 1997 (Box 7)
    - New Lots Avenue, Brooklyn, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Columbus Circle, 2001 (Box 7)
  - 20x24 digital prints: black and white Iris prints on watercolor paper from color negatives, 2002, 3 prints
    - Cars under the El, Brighton Beach, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Patty and Helen's Rooftop, Brooklyn, NY, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Backyard on Henry St., Brooklyn, NY, 2002 (Box 7)
  - 20x24 gelatin silver prints, 1988-2000, 18 prints
    - Brooklyn Bridge (Horizontal), 1997 (Box 8)
    - Lyceum Theatre, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Southwest Reservoir Bridge, 1996 (Box 8)
    - 79th Street Boat Basin, 1997 (Box 8)
    - New York Public Library, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Val's Rooftop, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Atlas Statue, 1993 (Box 8)
    - One Way, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Dave's Rooftop, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Ed and Paul, 1988 (Box 8)
    - House at Echo Lake, Vermont, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Paris: Pyramid at the Louvre, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Paris: Bridge with the Flying Birds, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Rome: The Pantheon, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Paris: Horse Shadow, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Paris: Rue de Rivoli, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Paris: Ferris Wheel from Eiffel Tower, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Paris: Jardin de Luxembourg, 1999 (Box 8)
  - 20x24 gelatin silver photographs, 1994-2002, 17 prints
    - Rue de Jarente, black and white, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Paris: Pont Neuf, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Queensboro Bridge, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Calvin Klein, Times Square, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Whippoorwill Lane, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Bridge with arches, Paris, 1998 (Box 9)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Sunset Park tree/vista, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Queensboro Bridge, from Manhattan, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Truck on Van Brunt Street, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Bryant Park, New York, 1994 (Box 9)
    - St. Marks Square in the rain, 2001 (Box 9)
    - The Empire State Building, 2002 (Box 9)
    - India Street Greenpoint, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Verona Street doorway, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Sugar Factory, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 9)
    - July Column, Paris, 2001 (Box 9)
  - 20x24 gelatin silver prints, 1995-1999, 4 matted prints
    - Ed's barn, Holland, Vermont, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Rockefeller Center, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Ferris wheel from the Tuileries, Paris, 1999 (Box 10)
    - Palais Royale, Paris, 1999 (Box 10)
  - 20x24 gelatin silver photographs, 1995-2001, 6 matted prints
    - Bridge to the Eiffel Tower (Pont d'Lena), Paris, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Red Hook Ducks, 1996 (Box 11)
    - The Flatiron Building, 1995 (Box 11)
    - St. Mark's Square from the Arcade, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Dancer on Front Street, Brooklyn, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Bush Terminal, Brooklyn, 1995 (Box 11)
  - 16x20 gelatin silver prints, 1989-2001, 13 matted prints
    - Riverside Park fog, 1997 (Box 12)
    - Graffitti wall, Tribeca, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Fifth Avenue rain, 1997 (Box 12)
    - Brooklyn Heights trees, 1996 (Box 12)
    - Riverside Park construction, 1995 (Box 12)
    - Fifth Avenue at 42nd Street, 1996 (Box 12)
    - Power plant, East River, 2001 (Box 12)
    - Walk New York, 2001 (Box 12)
    - People look at Los Angeles, 1997 (Box 12)
    - Staten Island Ferry, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Le Consulat, Paris, Montmartre, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Cummington, MA, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Morningside Park, 2001 (Box 12)
  - 11x14 gelatin silver prints, 1996-1999, 2 matted prints
    - Grand Central Station, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Fog, 1999 (Box 13)
  - 11x14 black and white digital print, 2001
    - Brooklyn Bridge with 9/11 Memorial Lights, 2001 (Box 13)
  - 20x24 color prints, 2002-2005, 8 matted prints
    - Columbus Circle, 2005 (Box 14)
    - Runner at The Reservoir, 2005 (Box 14)
    - Under the Henry Hudson Highway, 2005 (Box 14)
    - Red Rock West Café, 2002 (Box 14)
    - Fulton Landing Warehouse, 2002 (Box 14)
    - Taxi in Times Square, 2002 (Box 14)
    - Hamilton Avenue, 2002 (Box 14)
    - 125th Street, 2003 (Box 14)
  - 20x24 digital prints: black and white Iris prints on watercolor paper from color negatives, 2002, 2 matted prints
    - Ninth Street near Hamilton Ave., Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 14)
    - Smith and Ninth Street, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 14)
  - 20x24 gelatin silver prints, 1995-2002, 6 matted prints
    - Roosevelt Island Tram, 2002 (Box 15)
    - Trees/Brownstones, Downtown Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 15)
    - Statue of Liberty, from Red Hook, 2002 (Box 15)
    - Ethereal Ad/Times Square, 1995 (Box 15)
    - Water and Dock Streets, Brooklyn, 2002 (Box 15)
    - Evergreen Truck, Manhattan Bridge, 2002 (Box 15)
- Dark City: Urban America at Night, 2004-2015; 3 boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Color inkjet prints from the project that culminated in a book, Dark City: Urban America at Night. The 57 prints are accompanied by two color book maquettes (mock-ups) used to sequence the photographs; for the book design, Saville worked with well-known artist, educator, and designer Yolanda Cuomo of New York City.
  - 192 Dyckman St, Red Hook, New York City, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Park Construction, New York, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Former Warehouse, Columbus, Ohio, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Glass Storefront, Beverly Hills, California, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The Meadowlands, Secaucus, New Jersey, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The Green Hand, Portland, Maine, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Waring Envelope, Brooklyn, New York, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Twilight in Santa Monica "1160", 2004 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Construction, Gowanus, Brooklyn, New York, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Bushwick Warehouse, Brooklyn, New York, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Corner Carroll Gardens, Brooklyn, New York, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Girl on the Highline, New York City, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Brick Wall, Newark, New Jersey, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Bus Stop, Riverside Drive, New York City, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Space for Rent, New York City, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - String of Lights, New York City, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Baseball Field, Venice, California, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Billboard, I-95, Baltimore, Maryland, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Tribal Techno, New York City, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Breakfast Served Anytime, Detroit, Michigan, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Broom at W. 72nd Street, New York City, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Parking Garage, Detroit, Michigan, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Former Laundro Mat, Burlington, Vermont, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Hudson Street, New York City, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lobby, Amsterdam Ave., New York City, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Former Warehouse, Chicago, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - L.A. Corner Store with newspapers, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Former J.C. Penney, Columbus, Ohio, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Highline Alleyway, New York City, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Lighted Windows, New York City, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Mural Near Port Authority, New York City, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Driveway, Baltimore, Maryland, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Fairway Parking Lot Structure, New York City, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Former Clothing Store, Amsterdam Ave., New York City, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Glass Lobby corner of 6th Ave and 42nd St., New York City, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Greenpoint Warehosue (white one), 2014 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Main Street, Brooklyn (Nathalie), 2015 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Outskirts, Houston, Texas, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Warehouse District, Houston, Texas, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Construction Under the Manhattan Bridge, Brooklyn, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Seattle Wall, Seattle, Washington, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Cleveland City Banner, Cleveland, Ohio, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Stairway, Columbus, Ohio, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Former Dairy Bar, Detroit, Michigan, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Former Warehouse, Los Angeles, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Michigan Central Depot, Detroit, Michigan, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Orange Ladder, Greenpoint, Brooklyn, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - West 23rd St., New York City, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Road to Nowhere, Detroit, Michigan, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Corner Store, Burlington, Vermont, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Under the Highline, New York City, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Parking Garage, Houston, Texas, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Former Gas Station, Chelsea, New York City, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Greenwich Ave., New York City, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Columbia University Construction, New York City, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Simth and Ninth Street, Brooklyn, New York, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Former Jacks, Columbus, Ohio, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Small book maquette, color, with all textual content and images, for Dark City: Urban America at Night, circa 2014 (Box 19)
  - Full-size book maquette, color, with all textual content and images, for Dark City: Urban America at Night, circa 2014 (Box 20)
- Supplemental materials, 2011-2014
  - "Vacancy," from Journal de la photographie, artist statement and other materials, 2012 and undated (Box 17)
  - Profile, "Night Vision," in Photography Magazine, 2008 (Box 17)
  - Profile, "Night/Shift," Eyemazing magazine, 2009 (Box 17)
  - Portfolio, "Twilight Borders" and statement from the journal Exit #43: By Night, Madrid, 2011 (Box 17)
  - Exhibition list, 2014 (Box 17)
  - Traveling Through the Dark: The Night Photography of Lynn Saville, directed by Anna Boden, 2003 (Box 17, Optical-disc RL-01142-DVD-0001, Video-cassette RL-01142-vhs-0001)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original audiovisual media are closed to use. Contact the Rubenstein Library in advance to request the production of a viewing copy.
- Printed materials, 1998-2015
  - Book reviews, 2012
    - Review files (Box 17)
  - Book covers, 1998-2015; 8 folders
    Contains books published with covers featuring photographs taken by Lynn Saville.
    - The Night Game, Frank Golden (Box 18)
    - A Night in Brooklyn, D. Nurkse (Box 18)
    - Interrogating Water, Philip Fried (Box 18)
    - Big Men Speaking to Little Men, Philip Fried (Box 18)
    - Cohort, Philip Fried (Box 18)
    - Early/Late, Philip Fried (Box 18)
    - The Source of Life and Other Stories, Beth Bosworth (Box 18)
    - The Street Lawyer, John Grisham (Box 18)